sounds like a big statement that about
the most widely read classic
um but I have looked into that and there
are some interesting statistics on how
widely this was distributed at certain
times
and it's being translated into
many many many many many languages over
the years so yeah it says widely
distributed widely read
very sweet
do share your thoughts and feelings as
always
in the comments it would be lovely to
hear what you've thought of this
um of my reading of course
of any past experiences with this
any thoughts or Reflections it's lovely
to hear
your side of things
it adds so much more life and depth
to me on this side of the camera
and the microphone and the YouTube
yeah
I enjoyed that a lot very interesting
foreign lots to think about
those last few chapters particularly
really a lot to reflect on there
and the whole just the whole story I
find quite fascinating when you know
that the author himself was a pilot
piloted during the second world war as
well and died
as a result shot down
[Music]
um
and killed I think it was 1944 I think
it mentioned somewhere in the
introduction and I've been reading
around online as well
yeah July 1944 so
really feels like a lot of this is a
metaphor for certain experiences that
he's had and
The Little Prince
could represent
um
certain certain messages
that would have been happening that
would have been going on and manifesting
in his mind
during
an experience such as this where he's
had to perhaps crash land
um in the desert or
or wherever
okay I will leave it there for today
thank you so much to everyone that's
joined through
these five parts
those will remain on the channel you can
see my little introductions and the
little outros after each reading so
there was five separate readings this of
course
um originally it's the fifth but
um I will be compiling
these five videos into one long complete
audio book where I will cut out bits and
bobs
um add some soft music in between
um
maybe maybe between I'm not quite sure
we'll see how this works out but at
least at the beginning and at the end
and uh and this little reflection at the
end will remain
you take care
Wherever You Are
whatever you're up to
do take a look at my other videos audio
books
see what else you can find